



■ **BOD**: 24/07/1997

■ PHONE: 0774 6878 43

■ ADDRESS: Hồ Chí Minh

■ EMAIL: leminhtuan169@gmail.com

■ GIT: https://github.com/BryanLe97



CAREER GOALS

As a Fronted Developer with over 4 years of experience, I have a strong foundation in web technologies and a deep understanding of the user experience.

I can create responsive websites with various Javascript languages such as Vue.js.

In the next 3 years, I'd like to apply my experience and knowledge to contribute to creating value in terms of revenue and development for the company.



EDUCATION

Thu Duc Technology College

• 2015 - 2018

Chu Van An High School, Bien Hoa City

• 2012 - 2015



TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Language: Javascript, Typescript
- Framework: Vue (Vue3), Quasar, Element UI-(element plus), NuxtJS
- Build tool: Vite, Husky, Gitmoji, Lint-staged.



SOFT SKILLS

 Teamwork, Time Management, Hight Adaptability, Flexible, Problem - Solving, Data Driven.



WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER | OCT. 2020 - PRESENT GO2JOY VIETNAM JSC - https://joyinn.vn/

- Leading "Hotel In House/ Hotel Direction" Project: Building structure source and creating global component; Managing timeline and follow up the scope of work of team member.
- Leading "Admin Page" Project to set up product features: Convert Java code to pair Vuejs then upgrade Vue3.
- Leading "GoPMS Hotel Management System" Project: Optimize framework-Quasar, create product feature, co-op with the product team, UX/UI design.
- Developing a landing page for the marketing department;
- Convert from design/prototype to responsive interface on the web;
- Collaborate with the Product Owner, and UI/UX designer to find a solution for the feature;
- Researching, configuring, and applying build tools such as vite, husky, lint-staged;
- Optimizing website loading speed is better;

FRONT-END DEVELOPER | NOV. 2019 - OCT. 2020

GLINK SOLUTION CO. LTD

- Responsible for project maintenance both frontend & backend, debug, and fix bugs;
- Design logo and building website interface structure via Inkscape;

FRONT-END DEVELOPER | MAY.2018 - OCT. 2019

N.A.M TECHNOLOGY CO. LTD

- Researching and analyzing customer insight, creating a table structure to store product data and customer information;
- Developing the features to access the database (Add on, Delete, Edit);
- Developing product features such as login, payment, and product detail information;
- Building websites, developing features as required by other departments;
- Convert the design into a website interface; customizable and responsive to each device;
- Using tools to optimize data display in chart form: library chart.js;
- Use framework languages like NuxtJs (FE side) and NodeJS (BE side).